Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Resumes of Case (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Columbus, Delaware, and Marion Electric. Marion, OH., 239 (Reel 1)
  - Boilermakers v. Warren City Tank and Boiler. Toledo, OH., 240 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 335 v. Connersville Blower et al. Connersville, IN., 241 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Eugene Dietzgen. Chicago., 242 (Reel 1)
  - Retail Clerks, Local 424 v. Kroger Grocery. St. Louis, MO., 243 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 737 v. Northern Electric Railway. Syracuse, NY., 244 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 307 v. Morgan Engineering. Alliance, OH., 245 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Transue Williams Steel Forging. Alliance, Ohio., 246 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Linderman Steel and Machinery. Muskegon, MI., 247 (Reel 1)
  - Toledo Bridge and Crane v. Employees. Toledo, OH., 248 (Reel 1)
  - Molders v. Hurley Machine. Chicago., 249 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Zenith System. Tonawanda, NY., 250 (Reel 1)
  - Mechanics v. Steel Ship Link Belt. Chicago., 251 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Consolidated Car Heating. NA., 252 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Astoria Gas, Light, and Heat. Astoria, NY., 253 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Richards Iron Works. Manitowoc, WI., 254 (Reel 1)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, Local 386 et al. v. St. Louis Coffin. St. Louis, MO., 255 (Reel 1)
  - Leadburners v. Du Pont Powder. Hopewell, VA., 256 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Galveston Wharf. Galveston, TX., 257 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Atlantic Elevator et al. Minneapolis, MN., 258 (Reel 1)
  - Employers Association v. Union Carpenters. Poughkeepsie, NY., 259 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Quincy Railway. Quincy, IL., 260 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, District 77 v. Minneapolis Threshing Machine. Hopkins, MN., 261 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 764 v. Kansas City Railway. Kansas City, MO., 262 (Reel 1)
  - Kansas City Railways' Employees v. Kansas City Railway. Kansas City, MO., 263 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 770 v. Mobile Light and Railway. Mobile, AL., 264 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 199 v. Ottumwa Railway, Ottumwa, IA., 265 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 198 v. Hedrick Construction. Dallas, TX., 266 (Reel 1)
  - Shipyard Timekeepers, Locla 16164 v. Bethlehem Shipbuilding. Baltimore, MD., 267 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 381 v. Butte Electric Railway. Butte, Montana., 268 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Tredegar Iron Works. Richmond, VA., 269 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Smith and Wesson. Springfield, MA., 270 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Union 16087 et al. v. Walworth Manufacturing. Kewanee, IL., 271 (Reel 1)
  - Textile Workers v. Lorraine Mills et al. Pawtucket, RI et al., 272 (Reel 1)
  - Moran Towing et al. v. Board of Arbitration et al. New York City., 273 (Reel 1)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, Local 547 v. Montana Flour Mill et al. Great Falls, MT., 274 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees Divisions 669 and 737 v. Rochester and Syracuse Railway. Syracuse, NY., 275 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 580 v. Syracuse and Suburban Railway. Syracuse, NY., 276 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. Campbell Creek Coal. Dana, WV., 277 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Waynesboro Street Railway. Waynesboro, PA., 278 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 421 v. Shamokin and Mt. Carmel Transit. Mt. Carmel, PA., 279 (Reel 1)
  - Locomotive Engineers, Locals 419 and 868 v. New York Consolidated Railway. New York City., 280 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 62 v. Bass Foundry. Fort Wayne, IN., 281 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 797 v. Topeka Street Railway. Topeka, KS., 282 (Reel 1)
  - Messengers of American Railway Express v. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. La Junta, CO., 283 (Reel 1)
  - Fire Fighters Local 93 v. City of Cleveland. Cleveland, OH., 284 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Hudson Coal. Providence, RI., 285 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 681 and 737 v. Empire State Railroad. Syracuse, NY., 286 (Reel 1)
  - Hoisting Engineers v. Employers. Red Mountain, AL., 287 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Morrison Brothers et al. Dubuque, IA., 288 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Hatcher Tool. Detroit, MI., 289 (Reel 1)
  - Steam Fitters, Local 572 et al. v. Nashville Munition Plant. Nashville, TN., 290 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 441 v. Des Moines City Railway et al. Des Moines, IA., 291 (Reel 1)
  - Furnace Mens Union 271 v. Adrian Furnace. Du Bois, PA., 292 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 759 v. Lima Street Railway. Lima, OH., 293 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. New York Central Iron Works. Hagerstown, MD., 294 (Reel 1)
  - Timber workers Local 72 v. Blackwell Lumber. Coeur D'Alene, ID., 295 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Commercial Solvents. Terre Haute, IN., 296 (Reel 1)
  - United Mine Workers, Local 2050 v. Pittsburgh Coal, Pittsburgh, PA., 297 (Reel 1)
  - Textile Workers v. Swift Spinning Mills. Columbus, GA., 298 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 834 v. Columbus Street Railway. Columbus, GA., 299 (Reel 1)
  - Miners et al. v. Nevada Consolidated Copper. McGill, Ruth, and Ely, Nevada., 300 (Reel 1)
  - Ivers v. Tubular Rivet and Stud. Quincy, MA., 301 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Woonsocket Rubber. Woonsocket, RI., 302 (Reel 1)
  - Classified Laborers v. Treasury Department. San Francisco., 303 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. American Can. Geneva, NY., 304 (Reel 1)
  - Williamson Brothers v. Union Organizers. New York City., 305 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. War Department. Washington, DC., 306 (Reel 1)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators v. Theatrical Managers. Oklahoma City, OK., 307 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 558 v. Shreveport Railway. Shreveport, LA., 308 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 33 v. Price Electric. New Castle, PA., 309 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers v. Employers. Toledo, OH., 310 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Cosden Refinery. Tulsa, OK., 311 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. George W. Smith et al. Philadelphia., 312 (Reel 1)
  - Philadelphia Roll and Machine v. Molders Union. Philadelphia., 313 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. War Department. Washington, DC., 314 (Reel 1)
  - Blacksmiths v. Watertown Arsenal. Watertown, MA., 315 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 12 v. Poole Engineering. Baltimore, MD., 316 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. A.H. Peterson Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI., 317 (Reel 1)
  - Employees, Local 310 v. Hull and Dillon Packing. Pittsburg, KS, 318 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 829 v. Arkansas Valley Interurban Railway. Wichita, KS., 319 (Reel 1)
  - Elevators Operators and Starters, Local 495 v. Employers. San Francisco., 320 (Reel 1)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 227 v. Armour. Louisville, KY., 321 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Standard Boiler and Plate Iron. Niles, OH., 322 (Reel 1)
  - James McCurrach v. Neckwear Cutters. New York, NY., 323 (Reel 1)
  - Miners' Union v. Maplewood Sales. Peoria, IL., 324 (Reel 1)
  - Workers v. National Car Coupler. Attica, IN., 325 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. McIntosh Seymour. Auburn, NY., 326 (Reel 1)
  - Painters and Paperhangers et al v. Contracting Painters et al. San Diego, CA., 327 (Reel 1)
  - Interurban Trainmen v. Danville, Urbana, and Champaign Railway et al. Joliet and Springfield, IL., 328 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Third Avenue Railway. New York City., 329 (Reel 1)
  - Boilermakers, Local 127 v. Advance Rumley. Battle Creek, MI., 330 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Western Drop Forge. Marion, IN., 331 (Reel 1)
  - Foundry Employees, Local 66 et al. v. Baker Manufacturing. Saratoga Springs, NY., 332 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 414 v. Government Powder Plant. Nashville, TN., 333 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Pittsfield Machine and Tool. Pittsfield, MA., 334 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. American Locomotive Works. Paterson, NJ., 335 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Niles-Bement-Pond. Plainfield, NJ., 336 (Reel 1)
  - Trades Council v. Employers. Bay City, MI., 337 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Scullin Steel. St. Louis, MO., 338 (Reel 1)
  - Marie Martin et al. v. Spang and Company. Butler, PA., 339 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 312 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Rock Island, IL., 340 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 313 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Davenport IA., 341 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 599 v. Clinton, Davenport and Muscatine Railway. Muscatine, IA., 342 (Reel 1)
  - Building Trades Council v. Government Shipbuilding Contractors. Miami, FL., 343 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. American Bronze. Berwyn, PA., 344 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 752 v. Bloomington and Normal Railway. Bloomington, IL., 345 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 277 v. Niles-Bement-Pond et al. Ridgway, PA., 346 (Reel 1)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, Local 29 v. San Francisco Publishers Association. San Francisco., 347 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 85 v. Pittsburgh Railway. Pittsburgh, PA., 348 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 118 v. Eastern Pennsylvania Railway. Pottsville, PA., 349 (Reel 1)
  - Request of Ohio Electric Railway on Proposed Wage Scale. Cincinnati, OH., 350 (Reel 1)
  - Molders v. Hyde Windlass. Bath, ME., 351 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 183 v. Employers. Williamsport, PA., 352 (Reel 1)
  - Delbert Horton v. Wilson Body. Bay City, MI., 353 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Pacific Coast Steel. Seattle WA., 354 (Reel 1)
  - Firemen v. City Government. Kansas City, MO., 355 (Reel 1)
  - Molder, Local 70 et al v. Foundry men's Association. Boston., 356 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Thomas Iron Works. Allentown, PA., 357 (Reel 1)
  - Plumbers Division v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC., 358 (Reel 1)
  - Printing Pressmen's Union 1 vs. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC., 359 (Reel 1)
  - Steamfitters v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC., 360 (Reel 1)
  - Painters v. US Government Printing Office, Washington, DC., 361 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Detroit Forging. Detroit., 362 (Reel 1)
  - Foremen, Machinists et al. v. Niagara Falls Power. Niagara Falls, NY., 363 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 343 v. Kern Mutual Telephone et al. Taft, CA., 364 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Rock Island Southern Railroad. Galesburg, IL., 365 (Reel 1)
  - Plasterers v. Builders Exchange. St. Paul, MN., 366 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Pinkney Mining. Russellville, AL., 367 (Reel 1)
  - United Mine Workers, Locals 957, 599, and 1167 v. Sandor Engle. Glenlyon, PA., 368 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Bordberg Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI., 369 (Reel 1)
  - Watch Service Department v. Pullman. Pullman, IL., 370 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Union Salt. Cleveland, OH., 371 (Reel 1)
  - Railway Express Drivers, Local 720 v. Railway Express. Chicago, IL., 372 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Oklahoma Street Railway. Oklahoma City, OK., 373 (Reel 1)
  - Employees of Distribution Department v. Public Service Gas. Camden, NJ., 374 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 420 v. Elkhart Iron Works et al. Elkhart, IN., 375 (Reel 1)
  - Cigar Makers v. Pollock Company. Wheeling, WV., 376 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Starr Piano et al. Richmond, IN., 377 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. United Zinc Smelting. Moundsville, WV., 378 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Hoyt White Metal. Granite City, IL., 379 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Habirshaw Cable. Yonkers, NY., 380 (Reel 1)
  - Retort House Men v. Peoples Gas and Electric. Oswego, NY., 381 (Reel 1)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Anaconda Copper. Butte, MT., 382 (Reel 1)
  - Allied Shoe Workers v. Employers. Haverhill, MA., 383 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Studebaker Corporation. Detroit, MI., 384 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Sturtevant. Hyde Park, MA., 385 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Utah-Idaho Central Railway. Eureka, UT., 386 (Reel 1)
  - Coopers v. Sinclair Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 387 (Reel 1)
  - Baggage men et al. v. Consolidated Express. Indianapolis., 388 (Reel 1)
  - Blacksmiths v. Bedford Stone Club. Bedford, IN., 389 (Reel 1)
  - City Fire Fighters, Local 22 v. City of Philadelphia. Philadelphia, PA., 390 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Leeds and Northrup. Philadelphia., 391 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. J.G. Brill et al. Philadelphia., 392 (Reel 1)
  - Discharged Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, Pennsylvania, 393 (Reel 1)
  - Trainmen v. Ohio Valley Electric Railway. Huntington, WV., 394 (Reel 1)
  - Molders Local 417 v. Baker Manufacturing et al. Saratoga Springs, NY., 395 (Reel 1)
  - Typographical Union 16 v. American Newspaper Publishers. Chicago., 396 (Reel 1)
  - Conductors and Motormen v. Michigan United Railways. Jackson, MI., 397 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Buick. Flint, MI., 398 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati, Lawrenceburg, and Aurora Electric Railway. Cincinnati, OH., 399 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati Traction. Cincinnati., 400 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati and Columbus Traction. Cincinnati, OH., 401 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 631 v. Cincinnati, Milford, and Loveland Traction Company. Cincinnati, OH., 402 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Conestoga Traction. Lancaster, PA., 403 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Rock Island Southern Railroad. Rock Island, IL., 404 (Reel 1)
  - Blacksmiths, Local 455 v. Evansville Tool Works. Evansville, IN., 405 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 831 v. Louisville Street Railway et al. Louisville, KY., 406 (Reel 1)
  - Tin, Steel, and Granite Workers Union 10943 v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL., 407 (Reel 1)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Reading Iron. Reading and Danville, PA., 408 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Scranton Bolt and Nut. Scranton, PA., 409 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Eastern Steel. Pottsville, PA., 410 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA., 411 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Lebanon Valley Iron. Lebanon, PA., 412 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Burden Iron and Steel. Troy, NY., 413 (Reel 1)
  - Cohoes Rolling Mill et al. Cohoes, NY et al., 414 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters District Council v. Fabricated Ship. Milwaukee, WI., 415 (Reel 1)
  - Request of Tennessee Federation of Labor for Investigation at Old Hickory Powder Plant. Knoxville, TN., 416 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. War Department. Dayton, OH., 417 (Reel 1)
  - Asbestos Workers v. Stuart McGehee Construction. Camp Pike, AR., 418 (Reel 1)
  - Union Painters v. St. Louis Waterproofing. Urbana and Champaign, IL., 419 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Inland Ordnance et al. Bedford, OH., 420 (Reel 1)
  - Bricklayers v. American Car and Foundry. Berwick, PA., 421 (Reel 1)
  - Drop Forge Trades v. Billings and Spencer et al. Hartford, CT., 422 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Lodge 812 v. Knight Manufacturing. NA., 423 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 714 v. Cumberland County Power and Light. Portland, ME., 424 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Danville Street Railway. Danville, IL., 425 (Reel 1)
  - Tool Makers and Machinists v. Savage Arms et al. Philadelphia., 426 (Reel 1)
  - Motion Picture Exhibitors, Local 1 v. Motion Picture Machine Operators, Local 160. Cleveland., 427 (Reel 1)
  - Telephone Operators v. Dakota Central Telephone. Aberdeen, SD., 428 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 395 v. Aetna Foundry et al. Warren, OH., 429 (Reel 1)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Locals 253 and 254 v. Florida Phosphate Mining et al. Mulberry and Fort Meade, FL., 430 (Reel 1)
  - Labor v. Detroit Employers Association. Detroit, MI., 431 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers v. Intermountain Power. Spokane, WA., 432 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Public Service Gas, Newark, NJ., 433 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Philadelphia Railway. Philadelphia, PA., 434 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 687 v. Puget Sound Traction, Light, and Power et al. Seattle, WA., 435 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit., 436 (Reel 1)
  - Association of Employing Printers v. Printing Pressmen's and Assistants' Union, Local 23. New York City., 437 (Reel 1)
    3 pp.
  - Employees v. D.M. Dillon Steam Boiler Works. Fitchburg, MA., 438 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 721 and 724 v. Lewiston, Augusta, and Waterville Street Railway. Augusta, ME., 439 (Reel 1)
  - Bricklayers' and Masons' Unions v. Whitney and Company, New York City., 440 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. E.W. Bliss. Brooklyn, NY., 441 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Kingston Consolidated Railway. Kingston, NY., 442 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 826 v. San Diego Street Railway. San Diego, CA., 443 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. American Car and Foundry. Berwick, PA., 444 (Reel 1)
  - Boilermakers, Local 295 v. Stacy-Schmidt. York, PA., 445 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Western Knitting Mills. Rochester, MI., 446 (Reel 1)
  - Wage Scale--Nashville Railway and Light. Nashville, TN., 447 (Reel 1)
  - Emergency Employees v. Western Union Telegraph. Kansas City, MO., 448 (Reel 1)
  - Twin City Carpenters v. Employers. Minneapolis, MN., 449 (Reel 1)
  - Bakers, Local 17 v. Brennan Baking et al. Columbus., 450 (Reel 1)
- Resumes of Cases continued; Examiners Reports (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Montana Power. Lewiston, MT, 1 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rome Manufacturing. Rome, NY, 2 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rockport Granite. Rockport, MA, 3 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rome Locomotive. Rome, NY, 4 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rome Wire. Rome, NY, 5 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. United States Steel. Pittsburgh, PA, 6 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists v. H.W. Butterworth and Sons. Philadelphia, 7 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Bay State Tap and Die. Mansfield, MA, 8 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Haynes Automobile. Kokomo, IN, 9 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 397 v. Ann Arbor Machine et al. Ann Arbor, MI, 10 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 496 v. Berkshire Street Railway. Pittsfield, MA, 11 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 22 v. Milford, Attleboro and Woonsocket Street Railway. Worcester, MA, 12 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 22 v. Interstate Consolidated Street Railway. Worcester, MA, 13 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 22 v. Attleboro Branch Railroad. Worcester, MA, 14 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 22 v. Worcester Consolidated Street Railway. Worcester, MA, 15 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Butler Car Wheel. Butler, PA, 16 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Butler Bolt and Rivet. Butler, PA, 17 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Forged Steel Wheel. Butler, PA, 18 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Terre Haute, Indianapolis and Eastern Traction. Indianapolis, 19 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Interstate Public Service. Indianapolis, 20 (Reel 2)
  - Allied Metal Trades v. Hughes Tool et al. Houston, TX, 21 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Sioux City Service. Sioux City, IA, 22 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Westfield Manufacturing. Westfield, MA, 23 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters and Painters v. W.P. Richardson. Jacksonville, FL, 24 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Englehard Brothers. Evansville, IN, 25 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Meade Johnson. Evansville, IN, 26 (Reel 2)
  - Omaha Building Trades Council v. Luhr and Luhr Electric. Omaha, NE, 27 (Reel 2)
  - Punch and Shear Hands v. Submarine Boat. Newark, NJ, 28 (Reel 2)
  - Electrical et al. v. James Stewart, Contractors. Fayetteville, NC, 29 (Reel 2)
  - Painters, Local 694 v. Lakewood Hospital. Lakewood, NJ, 30 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Wright Martin Aircraft. New Brunswick, NJ, 31 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 579 v. Employers. Dubuque, IA, 32 (Reel 2)
  - Hooven, Owens, and Rentschlar v. Machinists, Local 241. Hamilton, OH, 33 (Reel 2)
  - F.J. Boyer v. J.G. White. Muscle Shoals, AL, 34 (Reel 2)
  - Photo Engravers' Local 5 v. John and Oliver Engraving. Chicago, 35 (Reel 2)
    1 p..
  - Employees v. Northern Cooperage. St. Paul, MN, 36 (Reel 2)
  - Bakery and Confectionery Workers v. Baking and Confectionery Companies. Philadelphia, 37 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Phoenix Mill. Evansville, IN, 38 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Akin-Erskine Milling. Evansville, IN, 39 (Reel 2)
  - Ship carpenters, Local 639 v. Henderson Shipbuilding. Mobile, AL, 40 (Reel 2)
  - Molders v. Union Iron Works. Decatur, IL, 41 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Illinois Southern Railway. Chicago, 42 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Detroit Rock Salt. Detroit, MI, 43 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Adirondack Power and Light. Glen Falls, NY, 44 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Standard Conveyor. North St. Paul, MN. Employees v. Sebring Pottery. Sebring, OH, 45 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Blackmer Post Pipe. St. Louis, MO, 46 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Grand View Fire Clay Miners. St. Louis, MO, 47 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Parker and Russell Mine and Manufacturing. St. Louis, MO, 48 (Reel 2)
  - Evans and Howard Fire Brick. St. Louis, MO, 49 (Reel 2)
  - Brick and Clay Workers v. Farber Clay and Mining. Farber, MO, 50 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. St. Louis Vitrified and Fire Brick. St. Louis, 51 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. LaClede Christy Clay Products. St. Louis, 52 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Walsh Fire Clay. St. Louis, 53 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Langlade Lumber. Antigo, WI, 54 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Frost Veneer Seating. Antigo, WI, 55 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Henshaw-Worden Lumber. Antigo, WI, 56 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Antigo Manufacturing. Antigo, WI, 57 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. English Manufacturing. Antigo, WI, 58 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Faust Lumber. Antigo, WI, 59 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rhinelander Refrigerator. Rhinelander, WI, 60 (Reel 2)
  - Link Belt v. Molder et al. Chicago, 61 (Reel 2)
  - Longshoremen, Local 1006 v. Spencer, Kellogg and Son. Superior, WI, 62 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Erie, PA et al, 63 (Reel 2)
  - Plasterers and Cement Finishers, Local 614 v. Nitrate Plant 2. Muscle Shoals, AL, 64 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Lee Brothers Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 65 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Mason-Donaldson Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 66 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. J.B. Roberts. Hochton, GA, 67 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Brown Evans Pants. Sedalia, MO, 68 (Reel 2)
  - Concrete Workers v. Employers. St. Louis, MO, 69 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Fuller Construction. Tyrone, PA, 70 (Reel 2)
  - Hydro-Electric and Power Company v. Linemen. Connersville, IN, 71 (Reel 2)
  - Molders v. Parker and Topping Foundry. Brainerd, MN, 72 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 275 v. Magnus Metal et al. Atlanta, GA, 73 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Montague Machine. Turner Falls, MA, 74 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists v. Williamsport Machine et al. Williamsport, PA, 75 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Foundries. Minneapolis, MN, 76 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rice Lake Lumber. Rice Lake, WI, 77 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Texas Steamship. Bath, ME, 78 (Reel 2)
  - Oklahoma Federation of Labor v. Shawnee-Tecumseh Traction. Muskogee, OK, 79 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Tennessee Copper. Copper Hill, TN, 80 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists v. Toledo Bridge and Crane et al. Toledo, OH, 81 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. C.C. Collins Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 82 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. W.T. Stevens Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 83 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Brown Land and Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 84 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Robbins Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 85 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Rhinelander Box and Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 86 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Brown Brothers Lumber. Rhinelander, WI, 87 (Reel 2)
  - Harbor Workers v. Boat Owners. New York City., 88 (Reel 2)